want to belabor the issue but i feel like this can be helpful in guidelines for ourselves in how we
enter into spaces of activism of support etc so i know a lot of people who are very um emphatically
supporting tiffany going to israel from the context of if she says that she needs to go
see with her own eyes what's wrong with that and you're right like on the surface like there
really isn't anything necessarily wrong with that in this particular instance it suggests
that the palestinian people who are actually sharing their own stories like in real time
that that's not enough of an information base it suggests that south africa who brought an entire
genocide case that like that's that they're they're not experts like it suggests that there is doubt to
be cast on victims and that's its own thing but i think what we can call attention to is that
if you want to go see something for yourself it is important in how you get that opportunity
and if you are given that opportunity paid by the occupier and while there you are occupying space
with the occupier in support of so doing comedy shows with known zionists who have said very hateful
and racist things about both black people and arabs and palestinians creating promotional content with
the same ilk if you are experiencing this by the resources of the occupier who is keeping those resources
from other individuals like palestinians can't come and see what it what's going on without actual fear
of death tiffany is able to come see what's going on because she identifies as jewish and because she is
famous it's important to acknowledge these points because it really helps us to understand when we want
to come into spaces what are ways in which we can enter that space that are not enabling and not
perpetuating the problem that made that space existent so again i i feel y'all like your best
of intentions are like nah like i would want to be able to come see with my own eyes too and i hear you
but it would be like going to a plantation because the slaver invited you there versus going to a plantation
with abolitionists who want to shut it down i hope this helps